[
     {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 1 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "20",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "20",
        "22",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 6 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "41",
      "options": [
        "41",
        "46",
        "43",
        "39"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 3 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "44",
      "options": [
        "49",
        "42",
        "46",
        "44"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 6 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "66",
      "options": [
        "68",
        "64",
        "71",
        "66"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 10 \u00d7 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "72",
      "options": [
        "70",
        "72",
        "74",
        "77"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 8 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "77",
      "options": [
        "75",
        "79",
        "82",
        "77"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 4 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "51",
      "options": [
        "53",
        "49",
        "56",
        "51"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 7 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "82",
      "options": [
        "87",
        "82",
        "80",
        "84"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 9 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "104",
      "options": [
        "109",
        "104",
        "106",
        "102"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 10 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "17",
        "20",
        "13"
      ]
    }
]